Antonio Margina

Moldova



marinel.margina@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/antonio-margina-32771b176

Summary

With 3+ years of experience in UX/UI Design and Front End Development, I've completed 2 successful projects while attending college. I've designed brands, developed websites, and improved SEO for businesses. Achieved a 230% increase in social media visibility. Seeking new opportunities to apply my skills in delivering intuitive user experiences and impactful designs.

Experience



BaitBoot

No Company

May 2023 - May 2023 (1 month)

This site was also developed by me from scratch. It was a task at my college I had to finish in 3 weeks (Design + Code). U can see the project if u check my Portfolio Profile: https://contra.com/antonyoUX

Web Developer

KeyCorp SRL

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023 (4 months)

I designed the site from scratch in Figma and then developed it using vanilla HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript.

Education



Centrul de Excelență în Informatică și Tehnologii Informaționale

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Web/Multimedia Management and Webmaster 2020 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications



The Complete Digital Marketing Course - Udemy

0004

Skills

Marketing • WordPress • English • Problem Solving • Strategy • Web Content Writing • Figma (Software) • Web Development